Guide to the UH Business Manager (McElhinney) Records
University of Houston Libraries
- Board of Regents, 1945-1973
  - Executive Committee and Building Committee, January 23, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Regents, February 7, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Building Committee, February 7, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Regents, March 7, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Building Committee, March 7, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Regents, April 4, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Building Committee, April 4, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Regents, May 16, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Building Committee, May 16, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Executive Committee, May 25, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Regents, June 6, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Building Committee, June 6, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Building and Executive Committee, June 20, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Building Committee, June 29, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Finance Committee, July 10, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Executive Committee, July 27, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Building Committee, July 27, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Regents, August 1, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Special Meeting, August 1, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - General Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Resolution - Sale and Endorsement of Securities, September 30, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Approval and payment of all accounts, December 14, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Local Fund Account, December 14, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Issuance of $300,000 promissory note, November 2, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Re-sale-securities Meeting, July 13, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Standing Committees 1966-1967, December 7, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Regents, September 5, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Building Committee, September 5, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, October 4, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee, October 25, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Regents, November 7, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Building Committee, November 7, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Building Committee, December 5, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Regents, December 12, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Building Committee, January 9, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Investment Committee, January 10, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Regents, February 6, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Building Committee, February 6, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Finance Committee, February 16, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Regents, March 5, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Building Committee, March 5, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Building Committee, April 11, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Regents, April 11, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Finance Committee, May 8, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Letter from C.F. to Investment Committee, May 9, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Regents, May 16, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Building Committee, May 16, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Regents, June 4, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Building Committee, June 4, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Building Committee, July 2, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Finance Committee, July 24, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Regents, August 20, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Building Committee, August 20, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Finance Committee, August 20, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Personnel List, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Resolution Regarding: Sale and endorsement of securities, 1966-1970 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Regents, October 1, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Building Committee, October 1, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Regents, October 29, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Building Committee, October 29, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Staff Conference Members, Dinner Meeting, October 29, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Regents, December 9, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Building Committee, December 9, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Regents, February 4, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Building Committee, February 4, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Finance Committee, February 5, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Regents, March 4, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Building Committee, March 4, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Regents, April 8, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Regents, May 6, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Building Committee, May 6, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Regents, June 3, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Building Committee, June 3, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Regents, August 5, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Building Committee, August 5, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Regents, September 16, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Regents, October 28, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Building Committee, October 28, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Finance Committee, November 6, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Regents, November 25, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Regents, November 25, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Building Committee, November 25, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Executive Committee, December 17, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Regents, January 6, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Building Committee, January 6, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Regents, February 3, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Regents, February 3, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Building Committee, February 3, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Regents, March 3, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Building Committee, March 3, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Executive Committee, March 6, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Regents, April 7, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Building Committee, April 7, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Regents, May 5, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Building Committee, May 5, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Finance Committee, June 10, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Regents, July 7, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Building Committee, July 7, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Finance Committee, July 14, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Regents, August 4, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Building Committee, August 4, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Standing Committees: Executive, Building, Finance, Investment, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Members, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Schedule of Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Regents, September 1, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Regents, September 1, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Building Committee, September 1, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Regents, October 6, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Regents, October 6, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Building Committee, October 6, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Regents, December 7, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Building Committee, December 7, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Regents, January 5, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Building Committee, January 5, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Building Committee, February 16, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Regents, March 2, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Regents, March 2, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Building Committee, March 2, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee, March 19, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Regents, April 6, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Building Committee, April 6, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee, April 22, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Regents, May 4, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Building Committee, May 4, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Regents, June 1, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Building Committee, June 1, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Resolution-Sale and Endorsement of Securities, June 1, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Executive Committee, June 9, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Finance Committee, June 29, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Executive Committee, August 18, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Regents, August 24, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Regents, August 24, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Regents, August 24, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Regents, August 24, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Building Committee, August 24, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Regents, October 5, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Building Committee, October 5, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Regents, November 2, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Building Committee, November 2, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Members, November 2, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Regents, December 7, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Building Committee, December 7, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Executive Committee, December 30, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Regents, February 1, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Regents, February 1, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Building Committee, February 1, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Regents, March 7, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Building Committee, March 7, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Building Committee, April 4, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Regents, May 2, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Building Committee, May 2, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Regents, June 20, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Building Committee, June 20, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - General Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Regents, August 1, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Building Committee, August 1, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Revised Resolution-Approved by Board, August 1, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Regents, September 25, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Building Committee, September 25, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Regents, November 7, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Building Committee, November 7, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Regents, January 9, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Building Committee, January 9, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - UH Resolution-Approval of Payments, January 9, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Regents, February 12, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Building Committee, February 12, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Regents, March 6, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Building Committee, March 6, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Regents, April 3, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Building Committee, April 3, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Regents, May 1, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Building Committee, May 1, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Regents, June 5, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Building Committee, June 5, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Members Expiring Dates, 1967, 1969, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - UH Board of Regents list, June 1968 and Feb. 1971 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Organization Chart Proposed, June 1950 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Act Creating the UH State-Supported Institution, September 1963 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Minutes-Special Meeting-Board of Regents, April 14, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Manual, January 1966 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Manual of the Board of Regents, January 1966 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Resolution Authorizing Time Deposit of UH Balances in the State Treasury, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Blank forms – Notary Statement, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - The Growth and Development of UH-summation, March 1927-May 1950 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Act Creating UH-State-Supported Institution, September 1963 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Staff Conference Meetings, 1956-1973
  This series, consisting of 180 folders of material, documents the meetings held by the President of the University with his key administrators. Included in this series are agendas, minutes, correspondence, memoranda, and reports. Major issues, such as construction, finances, KUHT, KUHF, the campaign for state support, student unrest in the 1960s and 1970s, and desegregation are addressed throughout this series. Folders are arranged chronologically.
  - Meetings, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Organizational Chart, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Meetings, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Meetings, 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Meetings, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Meetings, August 1960 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - A Study of Administrative Management I, August 1960 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - A Study of Administrative Management II, August 1960 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Meetings, September 1960 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Meetings, October 1960 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Meetings, November 1960 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Meetings, December 1960 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Meetings, January 1961 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Report to the General Faculty Meeting, February 3, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Meetings, February 24, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Meetings, March 1961 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Meetings, April 1961 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Meetings, May 1961 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Meetings, June-August 1961 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Meetings, September 1961 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Meetings, October 1961 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Meetings, November 1961 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Meetings, December 1961 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Publications Received by various offices, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Analysis of Operations in the Instructional Area, January 18, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Meetings, January 1962 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Visit to Graduate Research Center, February 21, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Meetings, February 1962 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Meetings, March-April 1962 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Meetings, May-June 1962 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Memo Re: TCOHE and NASA support, June 7, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Meetings, July-August 1962 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Meetings, September 1962 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Meetings, October 1962 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Memo Re: Computer Center from John C. Allred, November 12, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Meetings, November 1962 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Meetings, December 1962 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Student Activity Fee Allocation, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Meetings, January 1963 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Meetings, January-February 1963 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Memo Re: Capital Requirements, February 20, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Meetings, March 1963 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Meetings, April 1963 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Meetings, May 1963 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Meetings, June 1963 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Meetings, July-August 1963 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Clippings Re: State Support, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Proposed Houston Research Institute, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Self-Study Conference Report, September 22, 1963\ (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Meetings, September 1963 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Meetings, October 1963 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Meetings, November 1963 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Meetings, December 1963 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Meetings, January 1964 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Meetings, February 1964 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Meetings, March 1964 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Meetings, April 1964 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Meetings, May 1964 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Meetings, June-August 1964 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Organizational Chart, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Student Activity Re-allocation, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - UH Catalog, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Meetings, September 1964 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Meetings, October 1964 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Meetings, November 1964 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Meetings, December 1964 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Meetings, January 1965 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Meetings, February 1965 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Meetings, March 1965 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Meetings, April 1965 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Meetings, May 1965 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Organization Chart, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Meetings, June 1965 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Meetings, July 1965 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Meetings, August 1965 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Meetings, September 1965 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Meetings, October 1965 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Meetings, November 1965 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Meetings, December 1965 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Meetings, January 1966 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Meetings, February 1966 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Meetings, March 1966 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Meetings, April 1966 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Meetings, May 1966 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Final Report-Committee for Excellence, May 31, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Meetings, June 1966 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Meetings, July 1966 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Meetings, August 1966 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Meetings, September 1966 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - International Head start, September 1966 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Meetings, October 1966 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Meetings, November 1966 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Fringe Benefits Committee, November 1966 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Meetings, December 1966 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Meetings, January 1967 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Meetings, February 1967 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Meetings, March 1967 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Meetings, April 1967 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Meetings, May 1967 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Meetings, June 1967 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Changes in Code of Criminal Procedure, August 28, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Meetings, September 1967 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Memo Re: Charges for Staff and Faculty Parking, September 1967 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Meetings, October 1967 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Meetings, November 1967 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Meetings, December 1967 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Meetings, January 1968 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Meetings, February 1968 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Meetings, March 1968 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Meetings, April 1968 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Meetings, May 1968 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Meetings, June 1968 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Meetings, July 1968 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Report: International Student Problems, July 1968 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - Meetings, August 1968 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Statement Inviting Speakers to the Conference, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Meetings, September 1968 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Report: English Department Planning, October 7, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Report: Employee Benefits in Texas, October 8, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Report: Biology Department Planning, October 14, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Meetings, October 1968 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Meetings, November 1968 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Meetings, December 1968 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Meetings, January 1969 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Memos: RE: Downtown School, January 1969 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Computing Center, January-February 1969 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Meetings, February 1969 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Meetings, March 1969 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Meetings, April-May 1969 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Meetings, June 1969 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Meetings, July 3, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Meetings, July 1969 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Meetings, August 1969 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Meetings, September 1969 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Meetings, October 1969 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Meetings, Novemeber 1969 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Meetings, December 1969 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Meetings, January 1970 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Meetings, February 1970 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Meetings, March 1970 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Meetings, April 1970 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Meetings, May 1970 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Meetings, June 1970 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Meetings, July 1970 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Meetings, August 1970 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Meetings, September 1970 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Meetings, October 1970 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Meetings, November 1970 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Meetings, Dec. 1970 to Jan. 1971 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Meetings, February-March 1971 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Meetings, April 1971 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Meetings, May 1971 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Meetings, June 1971 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Meetings, July-August 1971 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Memo To: Staff Conference, September 22, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Meetings, September 1971 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Student Services Fee Allocation Procedure, October 28, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Meetings, October 1971 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Ad Hoc Committee – Student Fee Process, November 5, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Meetings, November 1971 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Meetings, December 1971 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Meetings, January 1972 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Meetings, February 1972 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Meetings, March 1972 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Meetings, April 1972 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Meetings, May 1972 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Meetings, June 1972 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Meetings, July-August 1972 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Contingency Fund Allocation Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Meetings, September 1972 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Meetings, October-November 1972 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Victoria University Committee Progress Report, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Meetings, January-February 1973 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Meetings, March-April 1973 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Meetings, May-June 1973 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Meetings, July-August 1973 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Affirmative Action Program, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Notes, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Proposed Health Center Pharmacy, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Short-term Loan Funding, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 62)
- Legislative Activities, 1958-1963
  This series contains [eighty-three folders] arranged chronologically and retaining the folder titles used by McElhinney. Included are reports, minutes, correspondence, memoranda, newspaper clippings, speeches, position papers, state publications, and related materials. This series documents the efforts of the University to achieve state support and status as a state university during the early 1960s and includes the reports sent to the University administration by Patrick J. Nicholson during the 1961 legislative session. Also included are the initial budget requests to the state by the University. One of the primary correspondents in this series is State Senator Robert W. Baker of Houston.
  - Tax Support File, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Meeting with Texas Commission on Education, November 17 and 18, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Finance, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Tax Support-General File, 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Tax Support-Texas Commission on Education, 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Speech on State Support-Gen. A.D. Bruce, January 6, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - List-19 State Supported Institutions, January 28, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - CF McElhinney General File, April 11, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Tax Support Memorandum, October 10, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Texas Commission Report and Recommendations, November 22, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - City of Houston: Re: Long term needs for land, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Proposed Bill- UH as fully state supported, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Commission on Higher Education-Optometry, 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Tax Support-General File, 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Statement-Dated-Estimated Funds-State Funding, January 30, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Legislative Reports-P.J. Nicholson, January 1961 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - C.F. McElhinney, Austin Trip, February 13, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - State Supported File, Beginning, February 1961 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Committee Amendment No. 1, April 1961 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Senate Bill (SB) No. 2, May 23, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - House and Senate Journals-57th Legislature, May 23, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Role and Scope of UH Mailed to Texas Commission, November 28, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Advisory Council of College Presidents, December 19, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Newspaper Clippings-State Support, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Newspaper Clippings-State Support, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - State Support, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Original Draft Senate Support Bill, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Revised Copy Senate Bill, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Committee Substitute for SB 2, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Reference Documents, 1959-1961 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Memos from Patrick Nicholson, 1961-1962 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Legislative Budget Board Austin, TX, 1961-1962 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Commission on Higher Ed. Correspondence, Dec. 1961-May 1962 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - 19 State Supported Colleges and Universities, 1961-1962 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Commission on Higher Ed. Quarterly Meetings, January 8, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Commission on Higher Ed. Called Meeting, January 29, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Commission on State and Local Tax Meeting, January 29, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Texas Ed. Agency Re: Joint Meeting, February 8, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Meeting-Mr. Vernon McGee and Tom Keel, March 19, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 39)